

CONTACT

+256-753079045 +256-762557651

✓ rodgersmugagga68@gmail.com

Mbarara-Uganda

https://rodgers-mugaggaportfolio.netlify.app/

SKILLS

- Project Management
- Web development
- Fullstack Developer
- Software Developer
- Cloud Developer
- Leadership
- Effective Communication
- Critical Thinking
- Digital Marketing

LANGUAGES

- English (Fluent)
- Luganda(Fluent)
- German (Basic)
- Lunyankole (Intermediate)

REFERENCE

Jjuuko Anthony

CEO - LWERUDESO

Phone: +256-772881694

Email: jjuukoanthony@gmail.com

MUGAGGA RODGERS

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PROFILE

Full-Stack Developer and software engineering student at Mbarara University of Science & Technology. Experienced in building high-performance web and mobile applications, API design, and clean, maintainable code. Skilled problem-solver and proactive learner with leadership experience as Speaker of MUCOSA, contributing to the tech community in Uganda and East Africa.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Rodvers Tech company Ltd.

2024 - PRESENT

Founder and CEO

Founded and lead Rodvers Company Ltd, driving digital transformation in Africa through custom software development, cloud solutions, IT consulting, and IoT integration for businesses, governments, and communities.

Lwerudeso

ICT & database support volunteer /
Assistant account

2023 - 2024

Supported organizations/school operations by managing databases, offering ICT support, and assisting with financial records.

Ensured data accuracy, resolved tech issues, and contributed to efficient, transparent organization/school administration.

Helped the organization/school embrace digital tools for smoother workflows and improved service delivery.

EDUCATION

Bachelors of Science in Software Engineering

Mbarara University of Science and Technology **GPA:** --

2024 - present

Uganda Advanced Certificate Examination

St. Henry's College Kitovu, P.O Box 64, Masaka

2022 - 2023

results 14

Uganda Certificate Examination

St. Henry's College Kitovu, P.O Box 64, Masaka

2017 - 2020

results 11